Seema Mittal

E:seema10mittal@gmail.com|M:9872788737

O Abohar, Punjab

Objective: To turn into an exemplification of all-rounder, convey more than my capacities and versatile in all circumstances.

Summary

Having 5+ years of experience as Senior Real Time Analyst, managing and ensuring service levels are achieved and site performance during the day to ensure effective management of call volumes. Self-motivated and committed team player with strong analytical, problem-solving skills and ability to adapt quickly to new environments.

Education

B.Tech (CSE):- Chandigarh Engineering College, Mohali (2012-16), 78%.

12th:- Government Girls Sen. Sec. School, Abohar (2012), 78%.

Matric: - Anmol High School, Abohar (2010), 82%.

Professional Expertise

- Managing call volumes, AHT, daily attendance, productivity, break schedules and intraday SL.
- Work closely with operations team to analyze and help improve their delivery processes.
- Prepare daily/weekly reports and maintain service levels to achieve company goals.
- Generate ideas for process and service improvement planning.
- Highlighting non adherence issues and behavioral issues.
- Runs and analyzes reports for scheduling to meet departmental productivity and profitability goals.
- Use trends and RCA reports to forecast requirements.
- Assist with projects and other duties as requested or assigned.
- Convey and Co-ordinate with internal departments.

Experience

Prometric Testing Pvt. Ltd. (Sep 2022 - Apr 2023)

Gurgaon

Role Name: - Senior RTA.

- Prometric is a leading provider of technology-enabled testing and assessment solutions to many of the world's most recognized licensing and certification organizations, academic institutions, and government agencies.
- ✓ I am working as Senior RTA for offshore client.

Responsibilities: - As a Real Time Analyst (RTA), I shall have to monitor the floor performance, prepare daily reports, achieve service level, manage breaks, daily attendance, highlight non adherence issues, manage employees' information changes and many other assignments as and when required.

Teleperformance SE (April' 2019 - Sep 2022)

Mohali

Role Name: - Senior Executive RTA.

Teleperformance SE is an omnichannel company headquartered in France. The company specializes in outsourced omnichannel customer experience management, also known as Business Process Outsourcing (BPO).

✓ I worked as Senior Executive RTA for Flipkart Process.

Responsibilities: - As a Real Time Analyst (RTA), I shall have to monitor the floor performance, prepare daily reports, achieve service level, manage breaks, daily attendance, highlight non adherence issues, manage employees' information changes and many other assignments as and when required.

Conneqt Business Support Services (Sept' 2017 - Nov' 2018)

Mohali

Role Name: - Customer Care Executive.

- Conneqt Business Solutions Limited, also known as TBSS, provides business support services. The company offers customer lifecycle management and business process management services.
- ✓ I worked as Customer Care Executive for Airtel Postpaid in the same organization for 1 year and 2 months.

Responsibilities: - Business Process Outsourcing, in which have to deal with customers from various places all over the globe, listen to their issues and resolve them in the best way possible.

Skills

- Great learning capacity, responsibility, strong execution, and critical thinking capacity.
- Strong Mathematical analytical, problem solving capabilities and resolution skills.
- ✓ Good communication and people management skills.
- Capacity to work under tight cutoff times, ready to persuade others, vigorous and ready to work under tension, and free.
- Client oriented, highly organized and mindful to details.
- Attention to detail and the ability to prioritize and meet deadline.
- Approachable and presentable.
- Solid association ability and good time management skills.

Co-Curricular Activities

- Worked as a Class Representative for three consecutive years in the College and was titled as the head girl in College Hostel.
- Main Member of organizing committee of College Annual Technical Fest 'Parivartan'
- ✓ Active participant in sports activities, dance, anchoring.
- Organize various events at team level.
- Dynamic volunteer of social activities to teach destitute children and an active Blood Donor.